mychinaunicom.com 2016-04-15

# Privacy Policy

China Unicom English Online Store (http://www.mychinaunicom.com) is hosted and managed by Beijing Unimobile Limited on behalf of China Unicom Beijing Branch. Beijing Unimobile Limited is a Chinese company, based in Beijing, China. The government license registration number of Unimobile is 110000410149158. 

Unimobile is committed to the privacy and security of your information. All data that we collect and process is stored on servers located in USA, a country that may not provide an equivalent level of data protection to the laws in your home jurisdiction. This Privacy Policy describes: 

• What information this website collects from you and how it is collected. 

• How this website uses your information. 

• To whom this website may disclose your information. 

• How this website protects your information. 

### Types of Information Collected

• Personal information. Your name, billing address, email, contact telephone number, products and services purchased by you from this site and payment details. This information is personal information associated with you. 

• Anonymous information. Information on how you use this website to help us develop and improve it, including details of your domain name and Internet Protocol (IP) address, operating system, browser version, cookie details, how long you stayed on a page, the route you took to navigate through the pages and the website that you visited prior to accessing our site. Please note that this information is anonymous and only used in the aggregate - it is not personal information associated with you as a specific person. 

### Use of Collected Information

Unimobile uses the information it collects to provide you with the China Unicom English Online Store services, as well as to personalize your visit to this website and to help us review, develop and improve the products and services we offer. This website may monitor and record e-mails and other communications between you and Unimobile for quality assurance purposes and to review specific transaction requests. 

We may share your information with third parties we engage with to perform services on our behalf. For example, we may share related logistics information, fulfilling and delivering packages, receiving packages, enabling access to affiliated business websites etc. However, we will not sell or loan your information to third parties unless we ask for your permission upfront. 

We may also use your contact information for marketing purposes - see the section titled Marketing below. 

### Disclosure of Collected Information

Unimobile will disclose your information under the following circumstances: 

• To respond to subpoenas, judicial processes, legitimate requests by law enforcement officials, or as otherwise required in order complying with applicable law 

• To our employees and agents to deal with any accounts, products and services provided to you by us now or in the future. 

• In order to help this website with fraud prevention, debt collection, credit management and emergency services and crime prevention purposes, we may disclose information about you and the conduct of your account to credit reference agencies, debt collection agencies, fraud prevention agencies, security agencies, financial institutions, emergency services and crime prevention agencies, and telecommunications companies. 

• To suppliers we engage to process data on our behalf. 

• We may use aggregate information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring web site usage in order to help us develop the web site and our service and may provide such aggregate information to third parties for example content partners and advertisers. These statistics will not include information that can be used to identify any individual. 

• We may collect ourselves and disclose personal information you have provided to persons or companies that we retain to carry out promotions and other activities for which you have registered or in which you have otherwise asked to participate. 

### Protection of Collected Information

Unimobile uses standard industry practices to protect the personal information you provide. Any information you send to this website is encrypted using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. This helps protect your information from being intercepted and misused by third parties when it is traveling over the Internet. When this website receives your information, it is stored on a secure server and is only read by authorized personnel. Please be aware that although this website take steps to create a secure environment for your personal information, this website cannot guarantee the security of any personal information you transmit online. This website will make reasonable attempts to notify you if there is a security breach involving your personal information which results in a risk of identity theft or as otherwise required by law. Please note that you are responsible for keeping your password secure and you should not disclose it to anyone (unless you want to authorize them to access your account and incur charges on your account). 

### Access to Collected Information

To find out what personal information this website has collected about you, email us at . If you become aware of any inaccuracies in the personal information you have provided to this website, you must notify us and correct them as soon as possible. 

### Marketing

This website may use your personal information to contact you with information about special offers and rewards (this may include special offers of other companies) and disclose your personal information to affiliates, sub-contractors and agents for these purposes. From time to time, this website and its affiliates and partners may contact you by mail, telephone, email, other electronic messaging services (such as text, voice, sound or image messages including using automated calling systems) or fax with information about products and services (including discounts and special offers). 

If you do not wish to receive marketing or promotional information from this website and its affiliates and partners, you must contact this website 

at: [OnlineStore@mychinaunicom.com](mailto:OnlineStore@mychinaunicom.com). Please note that this website does not market its services to or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. A customer must be at least 18 years old in order to use the China Unicom English Online Store services. 

### Browser Cookies

Browser cookies are small pieces of text stored by your Internet browser on the hard drive of the computer you are using to access this website. This website uses cookies to connect you and the information you have provided in order to provide you with personalized content and a better experience when you return. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies, although you can choose not to. If you disable browser cookies from your browser you will not be able to create a shopping basket or place an order. For further information about managing and disabling browser cookies, you should refer to your Internet browser's help section or user guide. There are also many resources on the Internet regarding browser cookies. 

### Links to Other Websites

The website may provide access to other third-party websites by linking to them. This website is not responsible for the privacy policies (including data protection and cookies), content or security of linked websites. 

### Contact

If you have any questions or comments regarding China Unicom English Online Store's Privacy Policy, please email us at [OnlineStore@mychinaunicom.com](mailto:OnlineStore@mychinaunicom.com).
